{
    "title": "Glory Part 1 (PG Edits)",
    "note": "Note that these are in order",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "What is an abolitionist?",
        "answer": "Someone who wants slavery to end."
      },
      {
        "question": "What battle is going on?",
        "answer": "The Battle of Antietam."
      },
      {
        "question": "Antietam was a very bloody battle.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "The Emancipation Proclamation was a military order to free the slaves in the:",
        "answer": "The Rebel States"
      },
      {
        "question": "Robert thought the window opening was...",
        "answer": "a gunshot"
      },
      {
        "question": "Racism only lived in the South.",
        "answer": "False"
      },
      {
        "question": "The black men of the 54th have similar backgrounds.",
        "answer": "False"
      },
      {
        "question": "The Confederate Congress threatened both black union soldiers and white officers who fought with them with:",
        "answer": "death"
      },
      {
        "question": "After Antietam, Colonel Gould Shaw knows how a real battle feels. So he is _________ his soldiers.",
        "answer": "preparing"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why did they whip the deserter?",
        "answer": "To keep others from deserting."
      }
    ]
  }
  